renofgood.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy

renofgood are committed to protecting your privacy online. Here we explain how we collect information, what we do with it and what controls you have. 

You can find all other information about our website in our Terms and Conditions and Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs). 

##  What data we collect            

Your personal data will be used to to provide the information, goods and services offered through our website to you, for billing and order fulfilment. 

We collect personal information through the use of             cookies and from the information that you send to us when you : 

  * Visit our website. 

  * Order products. 

  * Create an account. 

  * Join our email newsletter. 

We also monitor who uses our website. For example, we may collect information about you like the type of internet browser you use, the website from which you have come to ours and your IP address (the unique address which identifiesyour computer on the internet). This lets us improve our website. 

##  Privacy promise

We know how important it is to keep your personal information safe and secure online. Any information that we collect from you is held legally and we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. 

In order to serve you most efficiently, reputable third-party banking (including PayPal) and distribution institutions handle our credit card transactions and order fulfilment. They receive the information needed to verify and authorise your payment card and to process your order. All such organisations are under strict obligation to keep your personal information private. 

##  Security

###  Account security 

You are responsible for your account security, password and any activities on it. We are not responsible for anything that may happen if you do not protect your password or account. 

###  Site security 

Our website uses the highest level of security available for online shopping. Any personal information that you send is securely encrypted by a 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). In other words, the SSL mixes-up your data and stops it from being taken by anyone else. 

###  How to check that you are in a secure area 

Our Checkout is one example of secure area. There are two ways that you can check that the page has been encrypted and that it is safe for you to continue : 

  1. A padlock will be shown at the bottom of your screen. 

  2. Our website address, http://www.renofgood.com, will change slightly :  
The part of the address starting with http will change to https. You can find it at the top of your screen. 

##  Phishing scams

Phishing scams try and trick you into giving your personal or sensitive information to a fake person. - Usually by an email or phone call from someone pretending to be from a real company. 

**Do not share your personal information with anyone who calls and says that they are from renofgood**. If we need to get in contact,. 

Please tell our Customer Service Team straight way if you think someone is trying to trick you into giving them your details.  email the Customer Services Team. 

##  Contact Us 

You can get in contact with our Customer Services Team by telephone or email :paris@renofgood.com 

  * Email the Customer Services Team 

##  Your rights 

You have the right to ask for access to the personal data which we may hold or process about you. You also have the right to ask us to correct any mistakes in your data. 

###  Right to prevent marketing 

We offer an email newsletter and may use your data for marketing reasons. We never sell your data to anyone else. You have the right to ask us to stop using your personal data to send you the renofgood email newsletter. You can opt-out any time by using the 'Unsubscribe' link at the very bottom of the email. 

  * We may capture information about your visit that will help us to improve the quality of our service, or be used to present you with ads which are relevant to your browsing history when you visit other websites. 

We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. 

We may show you ads based on many factors, including demographic information and previous shopping history. renofgood use third-party vendors, including Google, to display ads on sites across the Internet. 

Users may control the ads they see on Google by muting or blocking ads from certain advertisersor by opting out of personalized ads in Google's Ads Settings. Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings. 

###  Product Reviews 

Around 2 weeks after purchasing your product, we may send you an email inviting you to review and rate any products that you purchased either online or in store. once submitted, it usually takes 72 hours for your review to appear on our website providing it adheres to our Publishing guidelines. Please do not include any personally identifiable information including your full name when choosing your username and writing your review. 

All reviews are submitted on the basis that renofgood may use the review as it sees fit and for any marketing or promotional purposes. 

If you require any further information on this service or wish to have your review removed, you can contact Customer services. 

##  Cookie policy 

renofgood cookies are read-only and set by our website. They cannot have a virus or get any personal information from your computer. 

###  What are cookies? 

Cookies are tiny text files saved on your computer when you go to some web pages. 

Any website can put cookies on your computer. But your browser (for example Internet Explorer, Google Chrome or Firefox), will only allow some cookies to protect your privacy. 

It is usual that a cookie will contain the following : 

    * A website address, for example www.renofgood.com. 

    * Its 'lifetime' (how long it will be held on your computer for). 

    * Its value, usually a unique string of letters and / or numbers. 

###  First-party and third-party cookies 

    * **First-party cookies** are saved to your computer by the website that you are on. 

    * **Third-party cookies** are saved to your computer by a website that gives content to the one that you are on. So, if you watch a YouTube video on our website, YouTube may save its own cookie to your computer. 

A website can only read the cookies that it makes. So, other websites cannot read the cookies we save to your computer and we cannot read any cookies saved by them. 

##  renofgood first-party cookies

These are the cookies set by www.renofgood.com : 

Cookie Name 

| 

Purpose   
  
---|---  
  
ASP.NET_SessionId 

| 

This cookie allows us to respond to the choices that you make on our website like "Add to basket". Without it, we wouldn?t know if one person or many were using our website and no one would be able to log in or buy anything.   
  
PHPSESSID 

| 

This cookie is similar to the ASP.NET_SessionId cookie, but is only saved to your computer if you browse pages on our website that come from Wordpress (for example the Get Crafty blog).   
  
craft 

| 

When you select an interest or add something to your craft drawer the craft cookie makes sure that our website will remember it.   
  
viewedproducts 

| 

This cookie is used to show your recently browsed items. You can hide Recent Items with the cross that appears as you pass your mouse pointer over them, or you can choose to ?Remove all?.   
  
Login 

| 

Thiscookie is set if you choose ?Keep me signed in? when you log in to your account. It keeps your account email address and a secure version of your password. Never choose 'Keep me signed in' on a public or shared computer.   
  
    * __utma 

    * __utmb 

    * __utmc 

    * __utmz 

| 

These cookies are set by Google Analytics and we use them for our website statistics. Any data that is sent to Google Analytics is kept secret. We only use it to better understand our visitors and make the right choices about our website and marketing.   
  
###  Third-party cookies

We keep our list of third-party cookies as up-to-date as possible. Our information may be wrong if our third-parties change their cookies and do not tell us however. 

Cookie set by 

| 

Name of cookies 

| 

Purpose   
  
---|---|---  
  
awin1.com (Affiliate Window) 

| 

aw3454 

| 

We work with other websites to try and bring more customers to renofgood. This cookie is only saved to your computer if you come to our website through one of these websites or their marketing. We use it when they send you to us so that we can pay them for your visit. Go to the Affiliate Window Privacy Policy, to understand how Affiliate Window use cookies.   
  
Facebook 

| 
    * c_user 

    * datr 

    * locale 

    * lu 

    * s 

    * xs 

| 

Facebook may save some or all of these cookies to your computer if you use the Facebook 'Like' or 'Share' buttons on the renofgood website. Go to the Facebook Cookie Policy, to understand how Facebook use cookies.   
  
Twitter 

| 
    * k, guest_id 

    * _twitter_sess 

    * original_referer 

    * external_referer 

| 

Twitter may save some or all of these cookies to your computer if you use the Twitter 'Tweet' button on the renofgood website. Go to the Twitter Privacy Policy, to understand how Twitter use cookies.   
  
PayPal 

| 
    * s_vi 

    * DH4puLeRqX6BpunfdurQO8Swi28 

    * HaC80bwXscjqZ7KM6VOxULOB534 

    * INSIDE_SEARCH_PARAMS 

    * KHcl0EuY7AKSMgfvHl7J5E7hPtK 

    * LANG 

    * PUuuwWB0yFt3AzV9ACftsAxz2fO 

    * SEGM 

    * cookie_check cwrClyrK4LoCV1fydGbAxiNL6iG 

    * flow_back_cookie 

    * login_email, navcmd 

    * navlns 

    * pNTcMTtQfrJuaJiwEnWXQ6yNxfq 

    * s_pers 

    * s_sess 

    * Apache, TS6a0e62 

| 

You will be sent to the PayPal website if you pay for your order from renofgood through them. This is so that you can log in and confirm your payment. PayPal save some or all of these cookies to your computer. Go to the PayPal Privacy Policy to understand how PayPal use cookies.   
  
##  Manage cookies on your computer or mobile device 

You can browse the renofgood website with no cookies allowed on your computer or mobile device, but you will not be able to add items to your wishlist or products to your shopping basket. 

In your web browser settings (for example Internet Explorer, Firefox or Google Chrome) you can : 

    * Check the cookies on your computer; 

    * remove all or some of them; and 

    * set rules on when you want cookies to be allowed. 

To manage cookies on your mobile phone, tablet or other mobile device we advise that you check the device manual. 

renofgood reserve the right to amend and update this policy. Any changes to our security and privacy policy will be posted on this page. The date of the latest update to this privacy policy is set out at the top of this page.
